海南省。二零二二年初中学业水平考试听力部分第一大题：听句子选图画。看图听句子，选出与句子意思一致的图画。每个句子读一遍。
第两大题：听句子选答语。根据你所听到的句子，选出正确的答语。每个句子。
Number 7 What's the weather like today?
What's the weather like today?
Number 8 I've got the first prize in the writing competition.
I've got the first prize in the writing competition.
Number 9 Let's meet at the bus stop.
Let's meet at the bus stop.
Number 10 I have a and I'm feeling awful now.
I have a headache and I'm feeling awful now.
Number Bob, what sports do you usually do?
第三大题：对话理解。根据你所听到的对话内容，选出能回答所提问题的最佳选项。每段。对话读两遍。听第一段对话。回答第十一和第十二小题。
I like swimming.
Sometimes I go running.
Running? I don't like it.
It's a little bit boring.
I enjoy table tennis.
I can play table tennis too.
Maybe we can play together.
Yeah. How about this Sunday morning?
Okay. I'll wait for you at school then.
Bob, what sports do you usually do?
I like swimming.
Sometimes I go running.
Running? I don't like it.
It's a little bit boring.
I enjoy table tennis.
I can play table tennis too.
Maybe we can play together.
Yeah. How about this Sunday morning?
Okay. I'll wait for you at school then.
听第二段对话。回答第3到15小题。
What can I do for you, madam?
I want to buy a TV set for my new house.
What kind of TV set do you like?
Actually, I haven't decided yet.
How about this one?
It sells well.
Erm, it looks small.
Do you have a bigger one?
Yes. Look. Here's a bigger one and it's only 4,000 yuan.
Good. I'll take it.
Thanks. We'll send you the TV set this afternoon.
What can I do for you, madam?
I want to buy a TV set for my new house.
What kind of TV set do you like?
Actually, I haven't decided yet.
How about this one?
It sells well.
Erm, it looks small.
Do you have a bigger one?
Yes. Look. Here's a bigger one and it's only 4,000 yuan.
Good. I'll take it.
Thanks. We'll send you the TV set this afternoon.
第四大题。一，短文理解。
Fourth Question Fourth Question The Fourth collection house.
根据你所听到的短文内容，选出最佳选项。短文读两遍。
A building of two floors.
We took the school bus and arrived at nine.
When we entered the
our eyes were caught by a collection of old photos.
Those photos told us something about the history of the town.
Then we went upstairs.
On the left, there were over 100 different clocks.
The oldest clock was already more than 200 years old.
On the right, there was a stone collection.
The stones were in different sizes, colours and shapes.
I really loved one stone that looked like a little rabbit,
which was eating a carrot.
The collections there were wonderful.
We stayed there until 11.
Everyone had a good time in the school trip.
This morning, we had a school trip to the Dashan Collection House.
A building of two floors.
We took the school bus and arrived at
When we entered the house, our eyes were caught by a collection of old photos.
Those photos told us something about the history of the town.
Then we went upstairs.
On the left, there were over 100 different clocks.
The oldest clock was already more than 200 years old.
On the right, there was a stone collection.
The stones were in different sizes, colours and shapes.
I really loved one stone that looked like a little rabbit,
was eating a carrot.
The collections there were wonderful.
We stayed there until 11.
Everyone had a good time in the school trip.
听力测试到此结束。
Thank you